okay this is U I'm going to call it the
uh American uh deadlift right cuz
America needs a a deadlift variation
anyway I don't like the Romanian
deadlift the way we currently do it
because you you're going to you know get
a strong Arch you know put your Lumar
spine into extension a little bit and
then anteriorly rotate your pelvis this
does a great job when you come down of
putting your hamstrings on stretch and
it really works the hamstrings down low
but as you come up if you keep this Arch
you can't really engage your glutes like
if I try and and Arch my low back and
anti rotate my pelvis I try and squeeze
my glutes right now they're soft I
cannot squeeze my glutes hard while
keeping a strong Arch so what I'm going
to do is I'm going to Arch when I come
down and get a big stretch and as I come
up I'm going to squeeze my glutes poster
rot the pelvis a little bit so you can't
go super heavy on this
but so Arch
[Music]
Str and this way you get the benefits of
really getting the hamstring down low
and the glutes up top to finish out the
lift anyway American deadlift hope you
liked it